Chibi Akuma(s) Episode 1: Title Screen!

Chibi Akumas Episode 2: Confrontation - Teaser Trailer 2
www.chibiakumas.com
#chibiakumas #chibi #akuma #retrogames #retrogaming #gothic #amstradcpc #8bit #チビ #ちび #悪魔 

レトロ8ビット弾幕STG「ちび悪魔」第２弾幕開けはあと少し！- ティーザーポスタ２
http://www.chibiakumas.com
#chibiakumas #chibi #akuma #retrogames #retrogaming #gothic #amstradcpc #8bit #チビ悪魔 #ちび悪魔 

Trailer:

At the end of 2016, the 'Chibi Akumas' game was released, 
bringing some of the craziest, weirdest, bullet-hell shooting
to the 8 bit Amstrad CPC...

but this autumn, Chibi Akumas is coming back, and things 
are about to become a whole lot more intense!

Better Graphics!

Crazier Enemies!

Bigger Bosses!

Heavier Firepower!

More Levels!

Multi-Direction Scrolling!

(Probably) The first CPC game with 256k enhancements!

Coming Halloween 2017

SAKUYA:
1234567890123456789012345678901234567890
Sakuya's had dreamed she could help others and save the town,
and she thought the Yuusha's could give her that chance,
Sakuya's nieve dream was destroyed, and her with it,
The innocent girl may be dead, something new has returned.

Sakuya's eye has been opened, and she's evolved to face the
reality that's been forced upon her, and this time, no-one 
will get in her way.

Calculating and ruthless, her immortality has elevated her beyond humainty, and she'll take whatever she wants, and next time someone is exploited, it won't be her...

Bochan:
1234567890123456789012345678901234567890
Bochan isn't the sharpest tool in the box, in
fact he's more a piece of gum in a world of 
scalpals!

Only really interested in playing or eating, he 
does not really have any anger, mallace or 
jealousy...  unfortunately, his sister has 
enough for two, and she often uses bochan to
her advantage.

While Bochan needs to feed on human flesh,
Unlike Chibiko, he can only eat decomposing 
flesh, and has no desire to harm the living,
and his needs are easily satisfied by the
abundance of graveyards and natural death.



YUMI:

A technical genious and millitary strategist of sorts - unfortunately his main priority seems to be the 
personal pride of victory, not actually saving those in need.


A firm believer that 'the lite sabre is the weapon of a true warrior'... there's no reason not to play it safe... so he carries a high-calibre 'Cobra Assault Cannon' rifle at all times!

YUME:

Master of Alchemy, spiritulist and chanellor - Also walks dogs and washes cars!

Gained her powers after developing a 'phillosophers stone' by chewing 5 flavours of bubble gum together for a full year.

She was banned from a neighbouring town after a rather unfortunate accident involving
300 litres of universal solvant which resulted in the creation of a volcano and killed half the population

Will do anything for money... Has a dangerous obsession with Pakurimon cartoons... she'd sell YOUR soul for more Pakurimon toys!

CHIBIKO:
1234567890123456789012345678901234567890
Chibiko may be cute, and her misdeed may only
be a result of her immaturity, however her actions 
are as brutal and remorseless as can be imagined


Her poor upbringing has caused her to be void of any
ethics, forethinking, or empathy for others. 
Worse still, As well as stopping the aging process, 
Her vampirism renders her unnable to mentally mature.

Wielding fearsome power, with no moral compass,
and no ability to comprehend the effect of her own
actions, Chibiko is devistating force to be reckoned
with.

Whatever happens next, the human race have a
real chalenge when it comes to dealing with this
little monster





Greetings,

I know we should be here to fight you,
but we can't be bothered!

Yumi's going to spend the day playing
'Idlemaster P4U', and I have to write 
my 'Noble Piece Prize' acceptance speech for
when I beat you!

Please come to our place - we'll fight there!

I have enclosed a crucifix that helps annoy you.


Yume 
  Yuusha.









Greek enemy ideas

Amphisbaena, a serpent with a head at each end.
Arachne, half-spider half-female, the mother of all spiders
Cerastes, spineless serpents with a set of ram-like horns on their heads.
harpy was a female monster in the form of a bird with a human face.

Flappybara - Flying Capybara!
Crocodile in a pot? Croc o croc

fFR065 [Yumi - Endsequence - challenge]




Eye Catch Lines:
Chibiko was a little monster when she was alive... Now she's undead there's going to be HELL to pay!!!
Chibiko's been to hell and back - and she's just warming up!
Yume's head is always in the clouds - unfortunately we're stuck with the rest of her!
Yumi's not the hero the town needs, deserves or even wants - but is probably all that's on offer!
They say only Death can cure stupidity - but nothing can stop bochan's stupid-power
In one instant, Sakuya will steal your heart! (and Lungs!)





Chibiko book ideas:
Extinction Level events - a practicle guide
The necronomicon - pop up edition
Genocide for dumbasses




[black screen]
Do you know where babies come from?
[childs bedroom]
Mom: Well, when a Mommy and Daddy who love each very much, that love becomes a seed, which grows into a baby!
Child: 'Kay... but where do baby VAMPIRES come from?
Mom:Well... when a Mommy and Daddy who don't love each other fuck while high on crack, 
and they have a child because they were to stupid to use protection,
and the child grows up unwanted and unloved, that child will grow up into a sadistic little shit 
who never learns empathy and only knows hatred and anger, and finally after she's tortured 
and maimed everything that's come across her path her body will become 
as dead and corrupted as her soul... and she'll become...

[Chibiko Full Screen - Massacre!]
Chibiko!
Holy Fucking Shit! I'm back! Welcome to Chibi Akumas Episode 2!
I bet you thought the last game was crazy, but you ain't seen nothing yet!
Huh? I know, you're wondering what happened to this village.
I bet you think *I'm* responsible for this... and that I killed all these people to drink their blood?
Well, you're WRONG!
I did it because I was bored. I'm not responsible for this... shitty TV scheduling is to blame here!
Well, anyway! Let's start the show!


Darwin's theory of evolution says that only the strong, and smartest will go on to survive

[Bochan licking lollipop - V1]

and the lazy and stupid will die out.

But sometimes, it's not so much 'What' you know, but 'who'

[black screen]
"What was that?"
"MMM!"
"Are you kidding me?"
"MMMM!
"Don't exagerate"
"MMMM MMMMM!"
"It'll only hurt for a moment! just hang on! Here we go"
(Squelch)

[Cut throat guy]

"Hmm? A slow one, that's going to take a while to fully drain"

[Chibiko by door] 

"Bochan.. I'm going to update the sign 'again' - You stay here... DON'T go anywhere!"
[bochan - TV]
Yeah Ookay!
[Chibiko by door Angry] 
"I mean it - DO NOT MOVE- You remember what happened last time"
Yeah Ookay!
[Chibiko by door Angry] 
"well whatever, if you do something stupid, I'm not coming to casualty to pick you up again, so you can have to get the bus home"
[Chibiko flying away from house 1]
[Chibiko flying away from house 2]
"Stupid brother, why do I have to put up with that retarded, idiot"
[Chibiko flying across rocky desert]
"He's got all the inteligence of a single cell amoeba!"
[Chibiko painting town sign]
[Stupid brother!]
[Chibiko painting town sign V2]
	[WELCOME TO NICOYAMA]->[WELCOME TO NIKUYAMA]
	[POPULATION 1043]-> [FOOD STORE 1043/2/1]

[chibiko Flying across desert reverse]
[I've got more important things to do than keep getting him out of trouble]
[chibiko Walking across train line]
"Huh?"
[chibiko Holding collar - big airline tag "Name:Bochan... Property of Chibiko" ]
[Chibiko Looking around - sees giant broken lollipop]
"You have got to be fucking kidding me."
[Black screen]
5 Minutes earlier
[bochan - TV - mischivous look on face]
[Bochan hand - holding flier 'massive lollipop sale!']
[bochan - TV - mischivous look on face]
"Lets go!"
[Candy Store 'Chompa Chumps' - Sign:Giant lolipop sale , sakuya in backgroun]
[Candy Store 'Chompa Chumps' - Bochan Inside]
[Candy Store - Bochan walks out with giant lollipop]
[Bocchan walks across traintrack]
[Bocchan walks across traintrack - drops lolipop on track]
[bochan lollipop - cant pull it up - starts licking it, while it's stuck to track]
[train coming - no movement]
[train closer - no movement]
[train Urgent - no movement]
[Train - Squelch]

[Chibiko with cart, random limbs sticking out]
Even the Darwin Awards aren't going to fucking believe this.
[Chibiko sewing foot - Cut fingers - Foot on backwards!]
Narration: For most people, their death would be the end.. but Chibiko would not let her brother just die!
[Chibiko Black mass]
Narration: So using dark forbidden magic! She brought Bochan back from the dead!
[Bochan resurrected!]
"But although he was back from the dead - brain death had set in, and his inteligence was greatly reduced..."
[Bochan licking lollipop - V2]
in theory
-------
[new characters in shadow]
"We're here at last! There it is! over in that valley"
"now we shall restore justice to this land!"

--------

[blood donation Chibiko and Bochan dressed as DR and NURSE - Sign says 'Blood Drive - Please give "J"enerously]
[blood donation tent - with bloodstained handprints - and graves behind it, some unfilled]
[Yume - challenge]
Yume: "We found you at last! evil being" 
[Chibiko - nurse angry]
Chibiko: Oh, shit, it's the  "shou-2-byou kyoudai"... piss off! we're to busy to waste time with you!
[Yumi - challenge]
Yumi: "Begone foul monster! You are not welcome here! I shall banish you from this land!
[Chibiko - nurse angry]
Chibiko: Yeah Right! My mother said that TEN YEARS AGO! she's long gone, and I'm STILL FUCKING HERE!
[Yume - challenge]
Yume: I see your corpseulent evil has spread to your stupid brother! No matter! I shall exorcise you both with my awesome spiritual powers!
[Chibiko - nurse angry]
Chibiko: Hey! Don't you call my brother stupid!
[Yumi - challenge]
Yumi: I shalt give thee one chance to leave, or my sister and I shalt bring the full force of our armies upon you and your brainless brother!
[Chibiko - nurse angry] (bochan by side)
Chibiko: DONT call my brother stupid!
[Yume - challenge]
Yume: some mini-vamp and her stupid brother are no match for the "Hero Twins"... once we defeat you to baka we'll be the saviors of the town!
[Chibiko - nurse angry] (bochan by side)
Chibiko: I told you not to call my brother stupid! right that's it! we're totally going to fuck you up - and your crappy 'army'!

--------------------------------
[Chibiko - victor smug]
Chibiko:Well, here we go! I've done all  5 levels, it's time for the final battle right?
[Yumi - Endsequence - announce]
Yumi:I think not! there is no way you can fight me, because, you see, I AM YOUR FATHER!
[Chibiko - victor confused]
chibiko: you what?
[Yumi - Endsequence - Smug]
...
[Chibiko - victor confused]
chibiko: er?
[Chibiko - victor angry]
chibiko: you gotta be kidding me? I seriously have to explain this?
[Chibiko - victor confused]
Chibiko: Uhh. 
[Chibiko - victor angry]
Chibiko: Yumi... you're EIGHT years old, and I'm NINE and a HALF! 
Chibiko: If you had spent even one nanosecond paying attention in either Maths or bioligy 
class you're realise how FUCKING STUPID what you just said was
Chibiko: I mean, you didn't just go FULL RETARD here, you cranked the retard dial up to 11, broke off 
the knob, and called all your retard friends around for a month long retard block party!
Chibiko: If you had even one atom of self respect you'd be so ashamed at what you just said you'd CUT OFF
YOUR OWN FUCKING HEAD to save yourself from living with the shame of how totally utterly, completely...

[Yume - Endsequence -  Shrug]
Yume: I'm sorry to interrupt this combo of lamest star bores joke, and epic chibiko rant, but can we get on with the final battle?

[Chibiko - victor smug]
Chibiko: well, if you want, but I've already whupped both your asses several times - so I don't think it'll last long

[Yume - Endsequence -  Shrug]
Yume: well, you won't be fighting us, We have brought someone back who's wants revenge on you!

[Chibiko - victor - confused]
Chibiko: someone I've pissed off? Well that just narrows it down to every life form on the plantet!

[Yume - Endsequence -  Smug]
Yume: remember Sakuya? who you beat in level 2? we've leveled her up to the max! and she's pretty angry with you?

[Chibiko - victor smug]
Chibiko: Sakuya? yeah right, I totally maimed her! they're going to need more than dental records to ID that!

[Yume - Endsequence -  The Machine]
Yume: Thanks to Yumi's technology, and my alchemy, nothing is impossible! Behold! the Resurrectifier 5000 PRO!

[Chibiko - victor angry]
Chibiko: You totally ripped that machine off from L-fin Lied!
[Yume - Endsequence -  Shrug]
Yume: No, we ripped it off from F.E.I.R ... they ripped it off 'L-fin Lied'
[Yume - Endsequence -  The Machine Engage!]
Yume: Behold! We brought Sakuya back! and now she is IMMORTAL!
[Sakuya - Foot]
[Sakuya - Waist]
[Sakuya - Chest]
[Sakuya - Wings]
[Sakuya - Face]
[Sakuya - TitleCard]
[Chibiko vomit]
Chibiko: JESUS FUCKING CHRIST! *I* just threw up in my mouth ... How? I don't even eat!

[Sakuya - Foot]
Chibiko: I mean, what the FUCK have you done? She is a TOTAL mess
[Sakuya - Waist]
Chibiko: and there's some nasty green shit leaking out of... well everywhere!

[Sakuya - Chest]
Yume: Well.. I'll admit it wasn't a 100% sucess, and I say Immortal, not Invincible!
[Sakuya - Wings]
Chibiko: it wasn't a 1% sucess! and whats all those shards of metal sticking out of her flesh
[Yume - Endsequence -  Shrug]
Yume: Now, she did that herself!... actually I think being brought back to life as a living rotting corpse
has caused her some mental problems

[Chibiko - victor angry]
Chibiko: Ya think? No Fucking Shit Sherlock!
Chibiko: I have to say, in the long history of 'yuusha twins' fuckups, I think this one takes the fucktard biscuit!
[Sakuya - Fury]
Sakuya: Chibiko! you Mother Fucker! You think you can just kill ME and get away with it?
Sakuya: You are an insect compared to me! I am destined to be the savior of mankind!
***
[Chibiko - victor angry]
Chibiko: Now you watch your lanugage! there may be minors playing this game! hey! are you even listening to me?
Editor's note! (this game is R-18)
[Sakuya - Eye Gouge]
Sakuya: H-e-y, bocha-n, you have such nice sparkly eyes, you could lend one to little me couldn't you
Sakuya: I mean, you don't need both do you? won't you give one to me!
[Chibiko - victor angry]
Chibiko: Get your filthy fingers OUT of my brother!
[Sakuya - Fury]
Sakuya: You mind your own business! You stupid little shit-bag!
[Chibiko - burning rage]
Chibiko: Do you have any idea who you're fucking with? I'm the biggest cause of premature death on this continent!
Chibiko: I hope Yume was right about you being immortal, because now I'm going to enjoy this!
Chibiko: One thousand years after I finish scortching the infestation of stupidity from the planet 
Chibiko: I'm still going to have just started work torturing you!
Chibiko: You're going to spend eternity begging me to kill you, to save you from the 
Chibiko: infinite kaliedoscope of suffering I'm going to inflict on you in the endless misery you'll call your existance!
[Sakuya - joking]
Sakuya: Ooh Chibiko! you're so fiesty! you say you can beat me... but you're completely underestimating the SIZE of the problem!
[Sakuya - grow]



----------------- Chibiko only version -------------
from ***
[Sakuya - Fury]
Sakuya: I'm going to rip you to fucking shreads you  syphilitic litte bloody cum-rag!  
Sakuya: I'm going to tear the life out of you! and then I'm going skin you alive, and then use your corpse as the centre piece in my living room!
[Chibiko - burning rage]
Chibiko: That IS IT!
Chibiko: Do you have any idea who you're fucking with? I'm the biggest cause of premature death on this continent!
Chibiko: I hope Yume was right about you being immortal, because I'm really going to enjoy this!
Chibiko: One thousand years after I finish scortching the infestation of stupidity from the planet 
Chibiko: I'm still going to have just started work torturing you!
Chibiko: You're going to spend eternity begging me to kill you, to save you from the 
Chibiko: infinite kaliedoscope of suffering I'm going to inflict on you in the endless misery you'll call your existance!
[Sakuya - joking]
Sakuya: Ooh Chibiko! you're so fiesty! you may think you can beat me... but you're completely underestimating the SIZE of the problem!
[Sakuya - grow]





--------------------------------
FR079 [Sakuya Explode 1]
[Chibiko and bochan endsequence - Chibiko smug]
Chibiko: so much for Immortal Sakuya! 
Chibiko: Well, I think we can conclusively say I beat you! now clear this mess up!
[yumi and yume - endsequence - gunk]
Yume: aarg! get me the disinfectant, there's gunk is in my ear!
Yumi:I cannot move!
[Chibiko and bochan endsequence - Chibiko smug]
Chibiko: Well that will teach you to be the extras, since I'm the main character, there's hardly any on me! Just like in toastbusters!
[[yumi and yume - endsequence  -  leave]
Yume:Come on Yumi, lets go, we'll take a bath, and start making new creatures for our next battle!
Chibiko: Yeah! shove off Losers!
Yumi: Yes, do not think you've heard the last of this!
[[yumi and yume - endsequence  -  leave question]
yume: Yeah! we'll be back for a rematch next weekend! I mean...  we can come right?
[Chibiko and bochan endsequence - Chibiko surprise]
Chibiko: Um, well I guess so... it's not like anyone else comes to visit.
Chibiko: Damn! why can't I get any proper friends?
[Chibiko and bochan endsequence - Bochan shrug]
Bochan: I wonder!


--------------------------------------------

[screen - fake end]
This room is an Illusion and 
is a trap devizedly by Jesus
Go ahead Dauntlessly! 
and play the whole flipping game again...
(sucker!)

[Bochan endsequence - NO!]
Bochan: Do what?... No! I'm not doing that!

[Yumi - Endsequence - challenge]
Yumi: But you must! It's the way of things!

[Bochan endsequence - NO!]
Bochan: It's dumb, and this game is boring already!

[Yumi - Endsequence - challenge]
Yumi: But the developers didn't make enough levels... you have to play the whole game again.
Yumi: And get all the big Diamonds... and XXX ... and buy all the DLC... and cut town the tallest tree in the forest with a herring!

[Bochan endsequence - NO!]
Bochan: Well I'm not doing it - so there!

[Yumi - Endsequence - confused]
Yumi: But the players not spent enough credits yet, and the developer has to pay the rent soon!

[Bochan endsequence - confused]
Bochan: Er, this isn't a real arcade game, it's consumer soft... there are no real credits!
[Yumi - Endsequence - confused]
Yumi: Hmm,That's a good point... just a moment... I shall have to consult my sister!
Yumi:Mumble mumble
Yume: I told you he wouldn't fall for it! really, play the whole game twice? I know he's stupid, but damn!

[Yume - Endsequence -  Shrug]
Yume:Well, Sorry about that interlude! pay no attention to the hero behind the curtain
Yume: I'm back, and I've brought an old friend whose just DIEing to MEAT you! 

[Bochan endsequence - confused]
Bochan:Huh? I don't have any friends :-(

[Yume - Endsequence -  Smug]
Yume:That was sarcasm! idiot... anyway, we've brought Sakuya back, and this time she's Powered up to the MAX!

[Bochan endsequence - confused]
Bochan:Sakuya, the annoying cosplay girl who can't sing?

[Yume - Endsequence -  Smug]
Yume:I don't think she's going to like you saying that! Behold! We have brought her back from the dead! and now she's Immortal!
[Sakuya intro]


[Bochan endsequence - confused]
Bochan: er, She's a bit messed up!

[Yume - Endsequence -  dejected]
Yume: I did the best I could, Ressurecting people from the dead and turning them into superhumans isn't easy you know!
Yume: Especially when there's pakurimon on half way through, and you.. um.. get destracted and forget about finishing it until the next day and all the ingredients have gone kinda soggy


[Bochan endsequence - smile]
Bochan: It's still a good effort!
[Yume - Endsequence -  dejected]
Yume: You think so?
[Bochan endsequence - smile]
Bochan: Yeah!
[Yume - Endsequence -  Shrug]
Yume: Thanks I try my best, but it's hard, and my pocket money doesn't stretch far enough to...

[Sakuya - Fury]
Sakuya: Would you two fucking annoying brats shut your putrid whining mouths before I rip out your spinal columns and use them to beat you both to death!
Sakuya: You are in prescence of the ressurection of the savior of mankind! Bow down and worship me puny mortals!

[Bochan endsequence - shock]
Bochan: Whoa! you really powered up her ego! she's now far more annoying!

[Sakuya - Fury]
Sakuya: How dare you speak to ME like that, You pitiful shit for brains fool! I'm going to take great pleasure in vivisecting your pathetic body and harvesting your organs for my own use!

[Bochan endsequence - shock]
Bochan: You're very rude! and I'm going to have to beat you up!
[Sakuya - joking]
Sakuya: my my! Such threats! What a naughty boy! I think I'm going to have to give you a SPANKING! 
[Sakuya - Smack!]
Sakuya: and I can assure you I'm going to make sure it hurts YOU a lot more than it hurts me!


--------------------------------
[bochan endsequence - bochan smug]
Bochan: Yeah! I win! I R the awesomeiest!

[yumi and yume - endsequence - gunk]
Yume: Well, I think I can safely say today did not go to plan!
Yumi: Our strategy was rather lacking in places it seems!
Bochan: It's sure a mess round here! your mom is going to be angry.
[bochan endsequence - bochan cautious]
[yumi and yume - endsequence - gunk]
Yume: Er, yes, I didn't think of that!
Yumi: We shall be grounded, for a century!
[bochan endsequence - bochan cautious]
Bochan: Well, I don't mind helping clean up!

[yumi and yume - endsequence - Gratitude]
Yume: Really? That's a big help!
Yumi: for a monster, you're quite the gentleman!
--------------------------------------------
